Ah Yeah…
Yo Yo Yo…
Gravity Gravity
Feel the power！
Save my love　すぐに
Save your dream with your dance
今夜だけ　解き放たれるPARADISE
探してるboy
愛の重さ感じながら
Go for the future
Open your eyes
Open your mind
Feel the power
Feel love
Fly so high
惹かれあうEach other
それが生み出すPower
You are my gravity gravity gravity
キミと行（ゆ）ける未来
今広がってく
（Let's try…）
You are my gravity gravity gravity
光求め飛ぼう　we can fly high
Make a move　もっと
Make your day as you want
夜を裂き　タイトに刻むParty tunes
止めないでboy
夢を信じる増やしながら
Get right together
Don't be afraid
Don't be shy
Keep the fire
Keep dream
Love so first
求め合うAnother world
So we get a fire
I'll be your gravity gravity gravity
昨日までのルール
今飛び越えてく
（Let's start…）
I'll be your gravity gravity gravity
自由のカタチさえ　we can change now
Gravity
Go！ Yes Alright
Don't stop the music now
さあ始まれ永遠（とわ）の運命
邪魔なヤツは撃ち抜け雷鳴命
Trans目覚める Transformer
恋から愛に Real変えて
HeatなHeartのBeatにHit
光りだすMirror ball
Gravity
以心伝心 意志Dancing
Pleasure Treasure
Gravity
Come on！
Everybody make some noise
無限に共に
Forever追えば
Enjoy炎上　舞え真上
Gravity Gravity
ずっと Gravity
You are my gravity gravity gravity
キミと行（ゆ）ける未来
今広がってく
You are my gravity gravity gravity
光求め飛ぼう　we can fly high
I'll be your gravity （Ah Yeah）
gravity （Oh Yeah）
gravity
昨日までのルール
今飛び越えてく
（Let's start…）
I'll be your gravity （Ah Yeah）
gravity （Oh Yeah）
gravity
自由のカタチさえ　we can change now
Gravity Gravity
Hey brother　夢のGraffiti
熱くWriting
We can do
Gonna be OK
全てを守れる盾になれ
Gravity Gravity
Hey sister　愛のGraffiti
強くLighting
We can do
Gonna be OK
全てを守れる盾になれ
Gravity Gravity
Hey brother　夢のGraffiti
熱くWriting
We can do
Gonna be OK
全てを守れる盾になれ
Gravity Gravity
Hey sister　愛のGraffiti
強くLighting
We can do
Gonna be OK
全てを守れる盾になれ
Ah Yeah…
Yo More high
Gravity Gravity
Ah Yeah…